Guide to the Dept. of Philosophy records, 1892-1952.
Dept. of Philosophy records, 1892-1952
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Dept. of Philosophy records, 1892-1952.
14-21-109
Cornell University. Dept. of Philosophy.
9.6 cubic ft.; 4 v.
Correspondence, syllabi, and other material.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Correspondence of the Sage School of Philosophy, including applications for fellowships and prizes, and material relating to the preparation of a history of the Sage School; correspondence pertaining to the publication of the Philosophical Review; syllabi and other material pertaining to the Dept. of Philosophy.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Correspondence of the Sage School of Philosophy, including applications for fellowships and prizes, and material relating to the preparation of a history of the Sage School; correspondence pertaining to the publication of the Philosophical Review; syllabi and other material pertaining to the Dept. of Philosophy.
Indexes to correspondence available in accession folder.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Cornell University. Dept. of Philosophy.; Sage School of Philosophy.
Titles:
Philosophical Review.
Subjects:
Philosophy--Study and teaching.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
CONTAINER LIST
- Correspondence
  - 1891-1895 (Box 1)
  - 1896-1912 (Box 2)
  - 1916-1917 (Box 2)
- Philosophical Review - correspondence misc.
  - 1892-1926 (Box 3)
  - 1927-1929 (Box 4)
  - 1930 (Box 5)
  - 1931 (Box 6)
  - Nov. 1931-July 1932 A-Z (Box 7)
  - Jan. 1932-Jan. 1935 A-N (Box 7)
  - Jan. 1933-Jan. 1935 O-Z (Box 8)
  - Jan. 1935-July 1936 A-M (Box 8)
  - Jan. 1935-July 1936 N-Z (Box 9)
  - July 1936-July 1937 A-Q (Box 9)
  - July 1936-July 1937 R-Z (Box 10)
  - July 1937-July 1938 A-Z (Box 10)
  - July 1938-July 1939 A-W (Box 11)
  - July 1939-July 1940 A-J (Box 11)
  - July 1939-July 1940 K-Z (Box 12)
  - July 1940-July 1942 A-O (Box 12)
  - July 1940-July 1942 P-Z (Box 13)
  - July 1942-July 1944 A-Z (Box 13)
- Philosophical Review
  - Misc., 1908-1949 (Box 14)
  - Correspondence, undated (Box 15)
- Sage School of Philosophy - correspondence
  - 1919-1920 A-Z (Box 16)
  - 1923-1924 A-Z (Box 16)
  - 1924-1925 A-Z (Box 16)
  - 1925-1928 A-Z (Box 17)
  - 1928-1930 A-Z (Box 18)
  - 1931-1940 Misc. A-L (Box 18)
  - 1931-1940 Misc. M-Z (Box 19)
  - 1935-1946 A-Z (Box 19)
- Other papers
  - Applications for teaching posts, 1928-1948 (Box 20)
  - Correspondence re: back issues, 1934, 1942, 1945-1947 (Box 21)
  - Correspondence, 1903-1907 (Box 21)
  - Hammond Questionaire, 1902 (Box 21)
  - Applications for scholarships and fellowships, A-Z, 1902-1906 (Box 21)
  - Philosophical Review - Accounts, 1945-1947 (Box 21)
  - Teaching positions, A-Z (Box 22)
  - Correspondence and recommendations, 1935-1952 (Box 22)
  - George Banta Publ. Co. correspondence (Box 23)
  - Banta bills, 1933-1945 (Box 24)
  - Cornell Philosophical Club Record (ms. vol.), 1894-1916 (Box 25)
  - Cornell Philosophical Club Record (ms. vol.), 1898-1900 (Box 25)
  - Cornell Philosophical Club Record (ms. vol.), 1934-1948 (Box 25)
  - Philosophical Review - correspondence (letter copy book), 1891-1898 (Box 25)